Tufts Weekly UP056
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Weekly, 1895 -- 1968; UP056.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 62 Volumes; 19.78 Gigabytes; 2079 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 28, 1935; UP056.001.027.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.07 Megabytes (Box 27)
    [Alpha Omicron Pi] Fashion Show.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 5, 1935; UP056.001.027.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.45 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 12, 1935; UP056.001.027.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.34 Megabytes (Box 27)
    American institute of electrical engineers
  - Tufts Weekly, December 19, 1935; UP056.001.027.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.61 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 9, 1936; UP056.001.027.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.29 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 16, 1936; UP056.001.027.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.82 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 23, 1936; UP056.001.027.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.96 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 13, 1936; UP056.001.027.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.10 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 20, 1936; UP056.001.027.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.72 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 27, 1936; UP056.001.027.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.04 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 5, 1936; UP056.001.027.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.29 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 12, 1936; UP056.001.027.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 16.75 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 19, 1936; UP056.001.027.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.78 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 26, 1936; UP056.001.027.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.00 Megabytes (Box 27)
    [All Around Club] Fashion Show (incl. photos).
  - Tufts Weekly, April 9, 1936; UP056.001.027.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.50 Megabytes (Box 27)
    Lester R. Adelson, 1935
  - Tufts Weekly, April 16, 1936; UP056.001.027.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.43 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 23, 1936; UP056.001.027.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 22.04 Megabytes (Box 27)
    [All Around Club] Hanry Cabot Lodge, Jr. is speaker. Tufts Weekly Pictoral Supplement.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 30, 1936; UP056.001.027.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.09 Megabytes (Box 27)
    [All Around Club] Hanry Cabot Lodge, Jr. is speaker.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 7, 1936; UP056.001.027.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.30 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 14, 1936; UP056.001.027.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.71 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 21, 1936; UP056.001.027.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.56 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 28, 1936; UP056.001.027.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 9.66 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 18, 1936; UP056.001.027.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.54 Megabytes (Box 27)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 24, 1936; UP056.001.028.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 1, 1936; UP056.001.028.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 8, 1936; UP056.001.028.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 15, 1936; UP056.001.028.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 22, 1936; UP056.001.028.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 29, 1936; UP056.001.028.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 5, 1936; UP056.001.028.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 12, 1936; UP056.001.028.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 19, 1936; UP056.001.028.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 26, 1936; UP056.001.028.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 3, 1936; UP056.001.028.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
    [Alumni council] Art fund established
  - Tufts Weekly, December 10, 1936; UP056.001.028.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
    [Alpha Omicron Pi] Sorority Formal.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 17, 1936; UP056.001.028.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
    Alumni relatives among undergraduates
  - Tufts Weekly, January 7, 1937; UP056.001.028.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 14, 1937; UP056.001.028.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 11, 1937; UP056.001.028.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 28)
    [Alumnae Hall] Kaye MacKinnon gives dance recital for benefit of Alumnae Hall; American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, February 18, 1937; UP056.001.028.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 25, 1937; UP056.001.028.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 4, 1937; UP056.001.028.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
    All Around Club. Alpha Tau Omega entertain fifteen children in "Big Brother Movement".
  - Tufts Weekly, March 11, 1937; UP056.001.028.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 18, 1937; UP056.001.028.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 25, 1937; UP056.001.028.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 1, 1937; UP056.001.028.00023 (Box 28)
    April Fool Issue.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 8, 1937; UP056.001.028.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 15, 1937; UP056.001.028.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 23, 1937; UP056.001.028.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 17 Megabytes (Box 28)
    American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, April 29, 1937; UP056.001.028.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 6, 1937; UP056.001.028.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 13, 1937; UP056.001.028.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 20, 1937; UP056.001.028.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 27, 1937; UP056.001.028.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 28)
    [Alpha Omicron Pi] Sorority formal, senior party.
  - Tufts Weekly, June 15, 1937; UP056.001.028.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 28)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 23, 1937; UP056.001.029.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 30, 1937; UP056.001.029.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
    President Cousins Memorial Issue.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 7, 1937; UP056.001.029.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
    Alpha Kappa Pi. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, October 15, 1937; UP056.001.029.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 21, 1937; UP056.001.029.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 16 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 28, 1937; UP056.001.029.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
    Academic Honors p. 1; Alumni council
  - Tufts Weekly, November 4, 1937; UP056.001.029.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
    Alpha Tau Omega members isolated because of diptheria quarantine
  - Tufts Weekly, November 12, 1937; UP056.001.029.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 18, 1937; UP056.001.029.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 24, 1937; UP056.001.029.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 2, 1937; UP056.001.029.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 9, 1937; UP056.001.029.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 16, 1937; UP056.001.029.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
    Roy Akagi speaker at Fletcher Scool on the Far East. Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, January 6, 1938; UP056.001.029.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 13, 1938; UP056.001.029.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 20, 1938; UP056.001.029.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 10, 1938; UP056.001.029.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
    Louis Abdu (A 1938, M 1942). Photo.
  - Tufts Weekly, February 17, 1938; UP056.001.029.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 25, 1938; UP056.001.029.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 3, 1938; UP056.001.029.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 10, 1938; UP056.001.029.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 17, 1938; UP056.001.029.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
    John Adams. Elected captain of Track for 1938-39.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 24, 1938; UP056.001.029.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 7, 1938; UP056.001.029.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 29)
    [All Aound Club] Elections and Activities. Alpha Kappa Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 14, 1938; UP056.001.029.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 21, 1938; UP056.001.029.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 29)
    [All Aound Club] Elections and Activities.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 28, 1938; UP056.001.029.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 6, 1938; UP056.001.029.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 12, 1938; UP056.001.029.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 19, 1938; UP056.001.029.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 26, 1938; UP056.001.029.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 14, 1938; UP056.001.029.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 29)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 1, 1938; UP056.001.030.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 6, 1938; UP056.001.030.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 13, 1938; UP056.001.030.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 20, 1938; UP056.001.030.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 30)
    Academic Honors. (Incl. photos - James G. Weldon and Persis Proctor) pp. 1, 2
  - Tufts Weekly, October 27, 1938; UP056.001.030.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 3, 1938; UP056.001.030.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 30)
    [Alumni council] Gift of college mace to President Carmichael [includes photo]
  - Tufts Weekly, November 10, 1938; UP056.001.030.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
    [All Around Club] Elections and Activites.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 17, 1938; UP056.001.030.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 15 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 25, 1938; UP056.001.030.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 1, 1938; UP056.001.030.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 8, 1938; UP056.001.030.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 15, 1938; UP056.001.030.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 13, 1939; UP056.001.030.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 19, 1939; UP056.001.030.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 9, 1939; UP056.001.030.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 16, 1939; UP056.001.030.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 24, 1939; UP056.001.030.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
    Alpha Kappa Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 2, 1939; UP056.001.030.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 9, 1939; UP056.001.030.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 16, 1939; UP056.001.030.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 23, 1939; UP056.001.030.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 6, 1939; UP056.001.030.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 13, 1939; UP056.001.030.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 21, 1939; UP056.001.030.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 14 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 28, 1939; UP056.001.030.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 4, 1939; UP056.001.030.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 11, 1939; UP056.001.030.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 18, 1939; UP056.001.030.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 25, 1939; UP056.001.030.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 2, 1939; UP056.001.030.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 20, 1939; UP056.001.030.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 30)
    Commencement Issue; Alumni council
  - Tufts Weekly, September 28, 1939; UP056.001.031.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 5, 1939; UP056.001.031.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 13, 1939; UP056.001.031.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 19, 1939; UP056.001.031.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 31)
    Academic Honors. p. 1, 4
  - Tufts Weekly, October 26, 1939; UP056.001.031.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 2, 1939; UP056.001.031.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 31)
    All Around Club. Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Xi Delta; Alumni council; American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, November 9, 1939; UP056.001.031.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 16, 1939; UP056.001.031.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 31)
    Alpha Omicron Pi; Alumni win awards at Columbia University School of Medicine
  - Tufts Weekly, November 23, 1939; UP056.001.031.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 31)
    All Around Club. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 30, 1939; UP056.001.031.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 7, 1939; UP056.001.031.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 31)
    All Around Club. Alpha Xi Delta. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, December 14, 1939; UP056.001.031.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 11, 1940; UP056.001.031.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 18, 1940; UP056.001.031.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 8, 1940; UP056.001.031.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 15, 1940; UP056.001.031.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 23, 1940; UP056.001.031.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 29, 1940; UP056.001.031.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 31)
    All Around Club. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, March 7, 1940; UP056.001.031.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 14, 1940; UP056.001.031.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 31)
    All Around Club. Alpha Omicron Pi. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, March 21, 1940; UP056.001.031.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 3, 1940; UP056.001.031.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 11, 1940; UP056.001.031.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 31)
    All Around Club (incl. photo- Florence Towle). Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 18, 1940; UP056.001.031.00024; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 31)
    Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, April 25, 1940; UP056.001.031.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 31)
    Alpha Xi Delta [photo of Marion Savage]. American institute of electrical engineering
  - Tufts Weekly, May 9, 1940; UP056.001.031.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 16, 1940; UP056.001.031.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 23, 1940; UP056.001.031.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, May 31, 1940; UP056.001.031.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, June 18, 1940; UP056.001.031.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 31)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 27, 1940; UP056.001.032.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 3, 1940; UP056.001.032.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 10, 1940; UP056.001.032.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 17, 1940; UP056.001.032.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club).
  - Tufts Weekly, October 24, 1940; UP056.001.032.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 31, 1940; UP056.001.032.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club). [All Around Club] Activities. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 7, 1940; UP056.001.032.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 9 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Academic Honors. pp. 1, 3
  - Tufts Weekly, November 15, 1940; UP056.001.032.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 21, 1940; UP056.001.032.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Freeland K. Abbott. (faculty), Review of "Confessions of an Individualist" by W.H. Chamberlin, p. 2.; Academic Honors p. 2 (ed)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 29, 1940; UP056.001.032.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 32)
    New Chapter Alpha Epsilon Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 5, 1940; UP056.001.032.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Freeland K. Abbott. (faculty), Review of "Confessions of an Individualist" by W.H. Chamberlin, p. 2.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 12, 1940; UP056.001.032.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 19, 1940; UP056.001.032.00013; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 32)
    New Chapter Alpha Epsilon Pi. Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, January 9, 1941; UP056.001.032.00014; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, January 16, 1941; UP056.001.032.00015; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 6, 1941; UP056.001.032.00016; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, February 13, 1941; UP056.001.032.00017; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club). Alpha Tau Omega. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, February 20, 1941; UP056.001.032.00018; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alpha Xi Delta. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Epsilon Pi New Chapter. Freeland K. Abbott. Comments on speech by William Y. Elliott.
  - Tufts Weekly, February 27, 1941; UP056.001.032.00019; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 6, 1941; UP056.001.032.00020; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 13, 1941; UP056.001.032.00021; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi New Chapter. Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club). Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, March 20, 1941; UP056.001.032.00022; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, March 27, 1941; UP056.001.032.00023; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alpha Xi Delta. Alpha Epsilon Pi New Chapter. Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club). Alpha Omicron Pi.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 1, 1941; UP056.001.032.00024 (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, April 10, 1941; UP056.001.032.00025; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 32)
    [All Around Club] Activities.
  - Tufts Weekly, April 16, 1941; UP056.001.032.00026; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Alpha Epsilon Pi New Chapter. Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club).
  - Tufts Weekly, April 24, 1941; UP056.001.032.00027; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 32)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club). Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 1, 1941; UP056.001.032.00028; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Alpha Tau Omega, dedicate main room to memory of Frank G. Wren
  - Tufts Weekly, May 8, 1941; UP056.001.032.00029; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alpha Tau Omega dedicate room to memory of Frank G. Wren; Alpha Omicron Pi. Academic Honors. pp. 1, 6 (incl. photos - Carol Barker and Eddie Dugger). Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club).
  - Tufts Weekly, May 15, 1941; UP056.001.032.00030; 1 Digital Object(s); 13 Megabytes (Box 32)
    Alexander Bain Society (Psychology Club). Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 22, 1941; UP056.001.032.00031; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 32)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, May 29, 1941; UP056.001.032.00032; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 32)
    New Chapter Alpha Epsilon Pi; Alpha Kappa Pi; Alpha Omicron Pi; Alpha Tau Omega; Alumni day
  - Tufts Weekly, June 16, 1941; UP056.001.032.00033; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 32)
  - Tufts Weekly, September 26, 1941; UP056.001.033.00001; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 33)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1941-1942. Alexander Bain Society. Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 2, 1941; UP056.001.033.00002; 1 Digital Object(s); 11 Megabytes (Box 33)
    Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Tau Omega. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, October 9, 1941; UP056.001.033.00003; 1 Digital Object(s); 10 Megabytes (Box 33)
    Alpha Epsilon Pi 1941-1942. Alexander Bain Society. Alpha Kappa Pi; [Alumnae Hall] projects to raise funds for Alumnae Hall
  - Tufts Weekly, October 17, 1941; UP056.001.033.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 33)
    Academic Honors. pp. 1, 4
  - Tufts Weekly, October 23, 1941; UP056.001.033.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 7 Megabytes (Box 33)
  - Tufts Weekly, October 30, 1941; UP056.001.033.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 33)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 6, 1941; UP056.001.033.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 33)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Suspended from interfraternity competition for infraction of rushing rules.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 14, 1941; UP056.001.033.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 33)
  - Tufts Weekly, November 21, 1941; UP056.001.033.00009; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 33)
    [Alumnae Hall] projects to raise funds for Alumnae Hall; Alpha Xi Delta. [All Around Club] Activities. Alpha Epsilon Pi 1941-1942. Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Tau Omega.
  - Tufts Weekly, November 27, 1941; UP056.001.033.00010; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Megabytes (Box 33)
  - Tufts Weekly, December 11, 1941; UP056.001.033.00011; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 33)
    Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Omicron Pi. Alpha Xi Delta.
  - Tufts Weekly, December 4, 1941; UP056.001.033.00012; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes (Box 33)
    [All Around Club] Activities. Alpha Kappa Pi. Alpha Omicron Pi.